{"data":[{"question":"No ink is ________ the pot.","a":"at","b":"in","c":"on","d":"over","answer":"2","explain":"\nPrepositions of Place: at, in, on \n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk... \n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry... \n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page... \n- Over:above or higher than something, without touching it.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"We are ________ work.","a":"at","b":"in","c":"on","d":"over","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Be at work = in the place where someone works","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"The cat is ________ the dog and the mouse.","a":"at","b":"over","c":"between","d":"in","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Between..... and.....: the distance between two places","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"His house is ________ the park.","a":"at","b":"over","c":"between","d":"opposite","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Opposite (preposition): on the other side of somebody or something","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"Tom is not my teacher but he is a friend of ________.","a":"me","b":"my","c":"I","d":"mine","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Mine (possessive pronoun): = my + Noun","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"Is that ruler yours or ________? It's ________, not mine.","a":"mine \/ your","b":"mine \/ yours","c":"my \/ your","d":"yours \/ mine","answer":"2","explain":"- Mine\/ yours (possessive pronoun)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"Who is that? It's ________ sister. ________ name is Anne.","a":"Mary's \/ Her","b":"Mary \/ Her","c":"Mary \/ Hers","d":"Mary's \/ She","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Mary's\/ Her: as adjective determiners (followed by a noun)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"This is John. He is a friend of ________. His wife is also ________ friend.","a":"my \/ mine","b":"me \/ mine","c":"mine \/ my","d":"yours \/ my","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Mine\/his\/hers\/its\/ours\/theirs: possessive adjective (pronouns are used in English to avoid repeating information that is already clear. In general it makes the sentence less confusing because the same information is not being repeated).\u00a0\n- My\/his\/her\/its\/our\/their: adjective pronoun: that modifies a noun by attributing possession (or other sense of belonging) to someone or something.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"Tom and Paul are ________ good friends. ________ are very kind to us.","a":"our \/ They","b":"our \/ Them","c":"our \/ Their","d":"ours \/ They","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Our: used as a adjective determiner (followed by a noun)\n- They: used as a personal pronoun (followed by a verb)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"The teacher is speaking. We must ________ to her.","a":"hear","b":"listen","c":"work","d":"talk","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Listen to someone: pay attention to what someone tells you and do what they suggest","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"}]}